//Create Questions
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Commonly used data types DO Not Include:",
        answer: "alerts",
        options: [
            "strings",
            "booleans",
            "alerts",
            "numbers"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed within ____.",
        answer: "parentheses",
        options: [
            "quotes",
            "curly brackets",
            "parentheses",
            "square brackets",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store _________",
        answer: "all of the above",
        options: [
            "number and strings",
            "other arrays",
            "booleans",
            "all of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "String values must be enclosed within ____ when being assigned to variables.",
        answer: "quotes",
        options: [
            "commas",
            "curly brackets",
            "quotes",
            "parentheses",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question : "A very useful tool used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
        answer: "console.log",
        options: [
            "JavaScript",
            "terminal / bash",
            "for loops",
            "console.log",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question : "What is the type of Pop up boxes available in JavaScript?",
        answer: "All the above",
        options: [
            "Alert",
            "Confirm",
            "Prompt",
            "All the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question : "Which one is a looping structure in JavaScript?",
        answer: "All the below",
        options: [
            "All the below",
            "For",
            "While",
            "do-while loops",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question : "What are the two basic groups of data types in JavaScript?",
        answer: "Primitive and reference types",
        options: [
            "Primitive and attribute",
            "Primitive and reference types",
            "Reference types and attributee",
            "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question : "Boolean operators that can be used in JavaScript include:",
        answer: "All the above",
        options: [
            "'And' Operator &&",
            "'Or' Operator ||",
            "'Not' Operator !",
            "All the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question : "Which one of these is not among the three different types of errors in JavaScript?",
        answer: "Animation time errors",
        options: [
            "Animation time errors",
            "Load time errors",
            "Run time errors",
            "Logical Errors",
        ]
    },
];